{
    "subject": "resource/Edgar_Rice_Burroughs",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Edwin_Lester_Arnold",
    "human_readable": "Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Edwin Lester Arnold.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9816660284996033,
            "question": "Can you name some works by Edgar Rice Burroughs that may reflect the influence of Edwin Lester Arnold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9800342321395874,
            "question": "What type of work did Edwin Lester Arnold produce that might have influenced Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9713723063468933,
            "question": "Do you know any examples of how Edgar Rice Burroughs acknowledged the influence of Edwin Lester Arnold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9607803821563721,
            "question": "Who was Edgar Rice Burroughs influenced by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9429627656936646,
            "question": "What is the significance of this literary connection between Edgar Rice Burroughs and Edwin Lester Arnold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9401058554649353,
            "question": "What other writers or influences might have shaped Edgar Rice Burroughs' work alongside Edwin Lester Arnold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859919309616089,
            "question": "Were there any specific themes or ideas in Edwin Lester Arnold's work that resonated with Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.857700526714325,
            "question": "Could you compare and contrast the works of Edgar Rice Burroughs and Edwin Lester Arnold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8125126957893372,
            "question": "How might Edwin Lester Arnold's work have shaped Edgar Rice Burroughs' writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5738379955291748,
            "question": "How might understanding this influence deepen our appreciation for Edgar Rice Burroughs' writing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Edwin Lester Arnold.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might Edwin Lester Arnold's work have shaped Edgar Rice Burroughs' writing style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you compare and contrast the works of Edgar Rice Burroughs and Edwin Lester Arnold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any specific themes or ideas in Edwin Lester Arnold's work that resonated with Edgar Rice Burroughs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7897_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found the following:\n\n* The documents discuss the literary influences on Edgar Rice Burroughs' works, particularly his Martian trilogy (A Princess of Mars, etc.).\n* Richard Lupoff is mentioned as suggesting that ERB was influenced by Edwin Lester Arnold's work, \"Gullivar Jones\".\n* However, another author (unnamed) disagrees with Lupoff's conclusion and argues that Edwin Lester Arnold is no Edgar Rice Burroughs.\n* The documents also mention Fritz Leiber making a case for Madame Helena P. Blavatsky as a source for ERB's works.\n\nGiven this information:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that supports the statement \"Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Edwin Lester Arnold.\" For example, it mentions that Richard Lupoff felt Burroughs was influenced by the fantasies of Edwin Lester Arnold. Additionally, there is a comparison between Gullivar Jones (by Edwin Lester Arnold) and A Princess of Mars (by Edgar Rice Burroughs), which suggests that Burroughs may have been influenced by Arnold's work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Edwin Lester Arnold's book \"Gullivar Jones\" lacks a captivating story and fails to match the literary quality of Edgar Rice Burroughs' \"A Princess of Mars\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}